# import requests

# response = requests.get("https://opentdb.com/api.php?amount=10&type=boolean")


question_data = {"response_code": 0, "results": [{"category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In Norse mythology, Thor once dressed as a woman.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Leonardo DiCaprio won an Oscar for Best Actor in 2004&#039;s &quot;The Aviator&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In &quot;Mario Kart 64&quot;, Waluigi is a playable character.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "Joseph Stalin&#039;s real name was Ioseb Bessarionis dze Dzugashvili.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "&quot;Undertale&quot; is an RPG created by Toby Fox and released in 2015.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Scottish producer Calvin Harris is from the town of Dumfries, Scotland.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Like with the Neanderthals, Homo sapiens sapiens also interbred with the Denisovans.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Faust is a playable character in &quot;Guilty Gear Xrd Revelator&quot;.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "It was once believed that injecting shark cartilage into people would prevent them from contracting cancer.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Sports", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Peyton Manning retired after winning Super Bowl XLIX.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Ashley Frangipane performs under the stage name Halsey.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Tony Hawk&#039;s Pro Skater was released in 1999.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Board Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The card game &quot;Munchkin&quot; won the 2001 Origins Award for Best Traditional Card Game.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "United States President John F. Kennedy was assassinated during his presidential motorcade in Atlanta, Georgia on November 22nd, 1963.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The term &quot;Spam&quot; came before the food product &quot;Spam&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In 2010, Twitter and the United States Library of Congress partnered together to archive every tweet by American citizens.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The Japanese god Izanagi successfully returned his wife Izanami from the Underworld.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The Sniper&#039;s SMG in Team Fortress 2, was originally intended to be the Scout&#039;s primary weapon.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "&quot;Mongolia&quot; was a part of the now non-existent U.S.S.R.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Gosho Aoyama Made This Series: (Detective Conan \/ Case Closed!)", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The anime Attack on Titan was directed by Tetsur\u014d Araki, the same person who directed the anime Highschool of the Dead.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Rabbits are rodents.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The name of the attack &quot;Kamehameha&quot; in Dragon Ball Z was named after a famous king of Hawaii.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "In Scandinavian languages, the letter &Aring; means river.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The Windows 7 operating system has six main editions.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "According to Greek Mythology, Atlas was an Olympian God.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": [
    "True"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The Hundred Years&#039; War was fought for more than a hundred years.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "For his performance at ComplexCon 2016 in Long Beach, California, Skrillex revived his &quot;Mothership&quot; set piece for one night only.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Pistons were added to Minecraft in Beta 1.5.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Sports", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In association football, or soccer, a corner kick is when the game restarts after someone scores a goal.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In RuneScape, one must complete the &quot;Dragon Slayer&quot; quest before equipping Rune Platelegs.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "All of these maps were in &quot;Tom Clancy&#039;s Rainbow Six Siege&quot; on its initial release: House, Clubhouse, Border, Consulate.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The USS Missouri (BB-63) last served in the Korean War.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Kiznaiver is an adaptation of a manga.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Resident Evil 4 was originally meant to be a Nintendo GameCube exclusive.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In &quot;Star Trek&quot;, Klingons are commonly referred to as &quot;Black Elves&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In &quot;Star Trek&quot;, Klingons are aliens.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Sports", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In Rugby League, performing a &quot;40-20&quot; is punished by a free kick for the opposing team.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "In Topology, the complement of an open set is a closed set.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The set of all algebraic numbers is countable.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Actor Tommy Chong served prison time.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Musical artist, Future, collaborated with Kendrick Lamar for the song: &quot;Mask Off&quot;.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "In the &quot;Kagerou Daze&quot; series, Shintaro Kisaragi is prominently shown with the color red.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Dave Grohl recorded the Foo Fighters&#039; debut, &quot;Foo Fighters,&quot; by himself.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Nutcracker Suite was one of the musical pieces featured in Disney&#039;s 1940&#039;s film Fantasia.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In the game &quot;Until Dawn&quot; Emily is the only playable character who can be killed by another playable character directly.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Minecraft wasn&rsquo;t the original name to Minecraft.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The Paradox Interactive game &quot;Stellaris&quot; was released in 2016.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Musicals & Theatres", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The protagonist&#039;s names in &#039;Who&#039;s Afraid of Virginia Woolf&#039;, George and Martha, were derived from George Washington and his wife.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "NCIS stands for &quot;Navy Corps Investigative Service&quot;", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]}
